xyo.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Digital Turbine | Digital Turbine

  * Customer Solutions __
  * Products __
  *  Case Studies 
  * About __
  *  Blog 
  * Login __

Digital Turbine, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Digital Turbine”, “We” or “Us”) recognize privacy as an important matter and have adopted this Privacy Policy to inform you of our data collection and use practices and confirm our commitment to keep your personal information secure.

Digital Turbine provides a broad mix of products and services through various channels. We provide products and services through websites we own or operate for our business partners (collectively, the “Digital Turbine Sites”). Certain products and services are primarily provided to our mobile operator and handset manufacturer partners, through software solutions of ours embedded in devices distributed by such business partners. Certain personal and non-personal information is collected and /or shared with us through products and services we provide we provide to end-users.

This Privacy Policy describes what user information we collect and store through the products and services we provide to our users and business partners, and how we use such information.

 **What We Collect**

We collect information through products and services We provide to better service our users and business partners. As part of our products and services, We receive personally identifiable information from wireless carriers and operators in order to provision specific content and data services. Two types of data and information are collected by Us or shared with Us:

Non-personal Information: which is non-identifying and non-identifiable information, without particular reference to the identity of the user from which such information was collected; and

Personally Identifiable Information: which is individually identifiable information that identifies an individual, or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, either alone or in combination with other information, or may be of private or sensitive nature. As part of our products and services, We receive Personal Identifiable Information from wireless carriers or device manufacturers or end users in order to provide the specific services requested by such business partners. Such personal information is acquired from either the wireless carrier or handset manufacturer, the user’s mobile device, or directly from the user, and may include service usage information such as call logs, websites visited, wireless location, application and feature usage, network traffic data, product and device-specific information and identifiers, service options the user chooses, mobile and device identifiers, and other similar information.

As our goal is to improve the features and usability of our products, We may also collect and analyze information available on a device such as which applications are used, downloaded and installed, and those which were deleted, as well as log information regarding the use of applications, purchase history (when applicable), wireless location, application and feature usage, network traffic data, product and device-specific information and identifiers, and service options you choose.

Our advertising partners may share with us information that describes how often users use their applications and information about events that occur within their application.

We may also use personal information which is shared with us by users of our services or visitors to our websites (such as name, email address or other address you provide, and any other information you provide us when you contact us for support or provide feedback), to respond to inquiries and to allow login with email address and social media accounts.

 **Information Collected On our Websites**

When you use our websites, information may be collected through cookies and web beacons about your device and your visit including browsing activity as you interact with our sites; IP address; and information about your connection, including your device’s browser, operating system, platform type and Internet connection speed. We use this information for operational, performance measurement and other business purposes; We also may use this information to assess the effectiveness of our sites and to help you should you request help with navigation problems on these sites.

Visitors or subscribers of our services may provide contact information through our websites in connection with purchasing or content access inquiries; to find out more about Digital Turbine, and to be contacted by a Digital Turbine representative. We may use this information to respond to your request, and for business purposes such as marketing and research. We will not rent or sell this information to other companies.

We do not set cookies as part of our media buying activities.

 **How We Use Collected Information**

We use the information We collect for the purpose of providing our products and services as well as perform analysis to improve our and our partners’ products, services and technologies. The information also enables targeting capabilities that are most likely suited for our business partners and device users. In addition, We use the information to analyze the performance of advertising campaigns of our business partners and to provide them with performance reports.

 **Who We Share The Information With**

We do not share the data which We collect or which is shared with us, with third parties other than our business partners and users of our products and services that are strictly related with such data. Our business partners then may use the data for various purposes, such as targeting applications, advertisements or other content. We may also use some of the data We collect that can be publicly disclosed to create industry reports, analyses, and similar materials that We may use for sales, marketing or other business purposes.

Please note that there are some exceptions where We may be obligated to provide data to third parties such as regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials when We believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure.

 **We respect ‘Do Not Track’ settings**

Users can indicate their privacy preferences through Limit Ad Tracking settings on iOS devices or Opt Out from Personalized Ads settings on Android devices. Whenever publishing partners pass us requests with the Do Not Track flag set, we do not retain any device-level data associated with the request.

Android Users

Ads Settings lets you opt out seeing personalized ads when you’re:

  * Signed in to your Google Account (“Ads Personalization”)
  * Signed out of your Google Account and browsing the websites and apps that partner with Google to show ads (“Ads Personalization Across the Web”)
  * Signed out of your Google Account and using Google Search (“Ads Personalization on Google Search”)

 _If you are signed in to your Google Account:_

 **Opt out of Ads Personalization**

  1. Go to [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/authenticated)
  2. Click or tap the slider next to “Ads Personalization”
  3. Click or tap **TURN OFF**

This opt-out will work across all of your signed-in devices when we recognize you as being signed-in.

 _If you’re signed out of your Google Account:_

 **Opt out of Ads Personalization Across the Web**

  1. Go to [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/authenticated)
  2. Click or tap the slider next to “Ads Personalization Across the Web”
  3. Click or tap **TURN OFF**

 **Opt out of Ads Personalization on Google Search**

  1. Go to [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/authenticated)
  2. Click or tap the slider next to “Ads Personalization on Google Search”
  3. Click or tap **TURN OFF**

 **iOS Users**

 _Opt-out of ads targeted based on your location_

You may choose to opt out of receiving location-based advertising and offers on your iOS device by opening “Settings”, tapping “Privacy”, tapping “Location Services”, tapping “System Services”, and sliding the Location-Based Apple Ads switch to “off”. Apple’s advertising platform does not receive location-based information when you turn off Location Services on your device.

 _Opt-out of targeted advertising_

You may choose to enable Limit Ad Tracking on iOS by opening “Settings,” then tapping on “Privacy,” then ”Advertising”, and sliding the Limit Ad Tracking switch to ”on”. To enable Limit Ad Tracking on Apple TV open “Settings”, select “General” then “Privacy”, and set “Limit Ad Tracking” to ”on.”

If you chose to enable Limit Ad Tracking, Apple’s advertising platform will opt your Apple ID out of receiving ads targeted to your interests regardless of what device you are using. Apps or advertisers that do not use Apple’s advertising platform are required to check the Limit Ad Tracking setting and are not permitted by Apple’s guidelines to serve you targeted ads if you have Limit Ad Tracking enabled.

Whenever you want to clear the data associated with your Advertising Identifier, you can simply reset it. To reset your Advertising Identifier on iOS, open “Settings”, tap “Privacy”, tap “Advertising”, and tap “Reset Advertising Identifier”. To reset your Advertising Identifier on Apple TV, open “Settings”, then select “General”, select “Privacy”, and click “Reset Advertising Identifier.”

When you enable Limit Ad Tracking, your advertising identifier is set to null for third party apps. It is automatically reset to a new random identifier when you disable Limit Ad Tracking.

If you enable Limit Ad Tracking, you may still receive the same number of ads, but the ads may be less relevant to you.

 **Security**

 **We take industry-standard security measures that include physical, administrative, and technical safeguards that are designed to protect the personal information that We collect and maintain. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.**

 **Contact Us For Any Questions or Concerns**

Please contact us at [privacy@digitalturbine.com](mailto:privacy@digitalturbine.com) with any questions about this privacy policy.

 **Changes To** **This Policy**

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If We do, We will post such changes on our homepage.

Effective October 14, 2016
